// Database Management System
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which type of data can be stored in the database?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Image oriented data",
      "Text, files containing data",
      "Data in the form of audio or video",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of database?.",
    answer: "Decentralized",
    options: [
      "Decentralized",
      "Distributed",
      "Hierarchical",
      "Network"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is a feature of DBMS?",
    answer: "Single-user Access only",
    options: [
      "Minimum Duplication and Redundancy of Data",
      "High Level of Security",
      "Single-user Access only",
      "Support ACID Property"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a feature of the database?",
    answer: "User interface provided",
    options: [
      "No-backup for the data stored",
      "User interface provided",
      "Lack of Authentication",
      "Store data in multiple locations"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a function of the database?",
    answer: "Analysing code",
    options: [
      "Managing stored data",
      "Manipulating data",
      "Security for stored data",
      "Analysing code"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is known as a set of entities of the same type that share same properties, or attributes?",
    answer: "Entity set",
    options: [
      "Relation set",
      "Tuples",
      "Entity set",
      "Entity Relation model"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is information about data called?",
    answer: "Meta data",
    options: [
      "Meta data",
      "Tera data",
      "Hyper data",
      "Relations"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The ability to query data, as well as insert, delete, and alter tuples, is offered by _________",
    answer: "DML (Data Manipulation Langauge)",
    options: [
      "TCL (Transaction Control Language)",
      "DCL (Data Control Language)",
      "DDL (Data Definition Langauge)",
      "DML (Data Manipulation Langauge)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "________ is a set of one or more attributes taken collectively to uniquely identify a record.",
    answer: "Super key",
    options: [
      "Primary Key",
      "Super key",
      "Candidate key",
      "Foreign key"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The top level of the hierarchy consists of ______ each of which can contain _____.",
    answer: "Catalogs, Schemas",
    options: [
      "Schemas, Catalogs",
      "Schemas, Environment",
      "Environment, Schemas",
      "Catalogs, Schemas"
    ]
  },
];